{"index": 1133, "title": "Paride ed Elena", "passage": "Paride ed Elena (] ; \"Paris and Helen\") is an opera by Christoph Willibald Gluck.  It is the third of Gluck's so-called reform operas for Vienna, following \"Alceste\" and \"Orfeo ed Euridice\", and the least often performed of the three.  Like its predecessors, the libretto was written by Ranieri de' Calzabigi.  The opera tells the story of the events between the Judgment of Paris and the flight of Paris and Helen to Troy.  It was premiered at the Burgtheater in Vienna on 3 November 1770.", "reason": "no_valid_qa_generated", "qa_list": [], "input_tokens": 1071, "output_tokens": 399, "total_tokens": 1470, "validation_info": {"invalid_questions": [], "missing_phrases": ["Elena", "Paris", "Helen", "Christoph Willibald Gluck", "third", "Gluck", "Vienna", "Alceste", "Orfeo ed Euridice", "three", "Ranieri de' Calzabigi", "Paris", "Paris", "Helen", "Troy", "Burgtheater", "Vienna", "3 November 1770", "title", "ed Elena\ncontent", "ed Elena"], "required_phrases": ["Elena", "Paris", "Helen", "Christoph Willibald Gluck", "third", "Gluck", "Vienna", "Alceste", "Orfeo ed Euridice", "three", "Ranieri de' Calzabigi", "Paris", "Paris", "Helen", "Troy", "Burgtheater", "Vienna", "3 November 1770", "title", "ed Elena\ncontent", "ed Elena"], "auto_added_phrases": [], "atomic_facts": ["Paride ed Elena is an opera", "Christoph Willibald Gluck composed Paride ed Elena", "Paride ed Elena is the third of Gluck's reform operas for Vienna", "Ranieri de' Calzabigi wrote the libretto for Paride ed Elena", "The opera tells the story of the events between the Judgment of Paris and the flight of Paris and Helen to Troy", "Paride ed Elena premiered at the Burgtheater in Vienna on 3 November 1770", "The libretto for Paride ed Elena was also written by Ranieri de' Calzabigi for Alceste and Orfeo ed Euridice"], "extracted_entities": [{"text": "Elena", "label": "ORG", "start": 17, "end": 22}, {"text": "Paris", "label": "GPE", "start": 54, "end": 59}, {"text": "Helen", "label": "GPE", "start": 64, "end": 69}, {"text": "Christoph Willibald Gluck", "label": "PERSON", "start": 87, "end": 112}, {"text": "third", "label": "ORDINAL", "start": 125, "end": 130}, {"text": "Gluck", "label": "PERSON", "start": 134, "end": 139}, {"text": "Vienna", "label": "GPE", "start": 170, "end": 176}, {"text": "Alceste", "label": "PERSON", "start": 189, "end": 196}, {"text": "Orfeo ed Euridice", "label": "WORK_OF_ART", "start": 203, "end": 220}, {"text": "three", "label": "CARDINAL", "start": 260, "end": 265}, {"text": "Ranieri de' Calzabigi", "label": "PERSON", "start": 319, "end": 340}, {"text": "Paris", "label": "GPE", "start": 407, "end": 412}, {"text": "Paris", "label": "GPE", "start": 431, "end": 436}, {"text": "Helen", "label": "GPE", "start": 441, "end": 446}, {"text": "Troy", "label": "GPE", "start": 450, "end": 454}, {"text": "Burgtheater", "label": "PERSON", "start": 481, "end": 492}, {"text": "Vienna", "label": "GPE", "start": 496, "end": 502}, {"text": "3 November 1770", "label": "DATE", "start": 506, "end": 521}], "spacy_relations": [{"subject": "Paride", "predicate": "is", "object": "opera", "relation_type": "SVO"}, {"subject": "Paris", "predicate": "Paride", "object": "Elena", "relation_type": "SVO"}, {"subject": "It", "predicate": "is", "object": "third", "relation_type": "SVO"}, {"subject": "opera", "predicate": "tells", "object": "story", "relation_type": "SVO"}]}}
{"index": 1754, "title": "Council of Forty-four", "passage": "The Council of Forty-four was one of the two central institutions of traditional Cheyenne Indian tribal governance, the other being the military societies such as the Dog Soldiers.  The influence of the Council of Forty-four waned in the face of internal conflict among the Cheyenne about Cheyenne policy toward encroaching white settlers on the Great Plains, and was dealt a severe blow by the Sand Creek Massacre.", "reason": "no_valid_qa_generated", "qa_list": [], "input_tokens": 959, "output_tokens": 5000, "total_tokens": 5959, "validation_info": {"invalid_questions": [], "missing_phrases": ["Forty-four", "The Council of Forty-four", "two", "Cheyenne Indian", "the Council of Forty-four", "Cheyenne", "Cheyenne", "the Great Plains", "the Sand Creek Massacre", "Council", "Forty-four\ncontent", "The Council"], "required_phrases": ["Forty-four", "The Council of Forty-four", "two", "Cheyenne Indian", "the Council of Forty-four", "Cheyenne", "Cheyenne", "the Great Plains", "the Sand Creek Massacre", "Council", "Forty-four\ncontent", "The Council"], "auto_added_phrases": [], "atomic_facts": [], "extracted_entities": [{"text": "Forty-four", "label": "CARDINAL", "start": 18, "end": 28}, {"text": "The Council of Forty-four", "label": "ORG", "start": 38, "end": 63}, {"text": "two", "label": "CARDINAL", "start": 79, "end": 82}, {"text": "Cheyenne Indian", "label": "PERSON", "start": 119, "end": 134}, {"text": "the Council of Forty-four", "label": "ORG", "start": 237, "end": 262}, {"text": "Cheyenne", "label": "GPE", "start": 312, "end": 320}, {"text": "Cheyenne", "label": "GPE", "start": 327, "end": 335}, {"text": "the Great Plains", "label": "EVENT", "start": 380, "end": 396}, {"text": "the Sand Creek Massacre", "label": "ORG", "start": 429, "end": 452}], "spacy_relations": [{"subject": "Council", "predicate": "was", "object": "one", "relation_type": "SVO"}]}}
